Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in what I do.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't wanna live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We believe in one another.
Jeez, they've really done it now.
This isn't good. What?
What are you talking about?
What isn't good?
What's going on with the bunnies?
Now!
We've got to run, Luffy!
We're running again? Where to?
Anywhere, as long as
it's far away from here.
Why?
Because there's about to be
an avalanche, that's why!
It's Wapol!
Wapol and his men have
come back to the island!
What?
They have?
Dalton headed up to Bighorn to meet them.
Anyone who can fight, grab a
weapon and head to Bighorn.
Hurry, everyone!
Get your weapons and head for Bighorn!
Follow Dalton all the way!
Follow Dalton to Bighorn!
Waple's back on the island!
Everyone arm yourselves!
We're going to protect our country!
Get a weapon!
March to Bighorn! Yeah!
Hey, Phoebe,
are you sure we're going
in the right direction
to get to this Gyasta
town where the witch is?
Well, now that you mention it, I'm
not exactly sure where we're going.
Well, we're in pretty bad
shape if you're not sure.
You know, if Luffy and Sanji
manage to make it to the castle?
And the doctor isn't there,
they'll just turn around and leave.
We have to make it to the
place, find the doctor,
and tell her to go back up the mountain.
Nami is running out of
time pretty quickly.
Yes, I realize that, Usopp.
Well, if you realize that,
then do something about it.
You're a princess, right?
What does that have to do with anything?
I can't snap my fingers
and make it happen.
I'm a princess, not a witch.
So what? Well, fine.
Why don't you go ahead and
take a look at the map?
Don't be ridiculous.
What am I supposed to do with that?
There's snow covering everything.
At any rate, if we keep to this route,
we should see a sign for this
piasta place somewhere along it.
Keep your eyes open.
Sure thing.
Just leave it to me.
I'll watch for signs of the sun.
There's no way I'll miss it.
That was delicious.
Listen closely, citizens.
Everything in this country can be
made into my snack if I want it to be.
Because I am a great man.
Do you know why I'm great?
Kurumaiimo, explain to them the reason.
Of course.
You're the greatest man in this country
because you are the king, your highness.
That's right.
Exactly right.
So if I want to eat a house, I
expect it to be served to my liking.
Yes, sir!
Wapol, sir.
I have some information for you.
What now?
I have received a report that
some of the Straw Hat brats very
inconsiderately set out for Drum Castle
after they arrived on the island,
Your Highness.
What?
Why'd they do that?
It appears that they took a sick woman
up the mountain to see her doctor.
What?
Really?
That was a dumb idea.
No one lives there now,
especially not a doctor.
Um, well, I actually heard that Dr.
Kureha, also very inconsiderately,
is currently living in Drum Castle.
She's a crazy old hag.
What did you say?
That woman is living in my castle?
How dare she mock me in such a way?
Kick her out!
I'll eat her up along with Straw Hat.
That'll show them.
Men, we're going back to the castle!
Yes, sir!
I don't think so.
Who was that?
He caught me!
I'm gonna die!
It's Dalton!
I came to see you dead, so
that really suits me just fine.
Dalton, you bastard!
It's a shame that you're still alive.
You just entered your own king.
It shouldn't be difficult to fix.
After all,
we live in an advanced
medical nation with almost two
dozen well-qualified doctors
to service his every need.
Yeah, that's right.
20 MDs emergency medical unit,
prepare! Heel, heel! Start operation.
Start operation.
Scalpel, needle, thin, and hammer.
Wow!
I was sure I was going to
die for a minute there!
This is a perfect
example of our situation.
You receive all the medical
attention that you could possibly
need while your citizens have
to suffer without a doctor.
It's wrong. It's wrong?
Show some respect.
I am still your king, Dalton.
He's right.
You'll shut your mouth if
you know what's good for you.
The three of us, including you, were in
the highest position among Waple's men.
We were his loyal servants,
or have you forgotten?
I haven't forgotten.
It's true that while you were
making our people suffer,
or all I could do is stand there as one of
Waple's men and watch as
you ruined our country.
I have to accept responsibility for that.
So, Wapol, let's leave
this country together.
We can't stay in the land
we betrayed any longer.
No, Dalton, wait!
You didn't do anything wrong!
He's right!
You're the only one in the
government who tried to protect us!
You're the only one who fought for us
while he was destroying the kingdom!
You stood up for us! Ha!
You should have died, Dalton,
and your post is captain of the
Drum Kingdom Security Guard!
I don't know how you all survived
in this country without any doctors.
Our country is internationally acknowledged
for its development in medicine,
but that renown is nothing
more than a cheap charade.
No one could guess that there
are actually only 20 doctors
who were shut up doing
research in the King's own lab,
and that all the other doctors
have been exiled from the country?
leaving the citizens to suffer.
Yes!
Anyone who gets sick or injured must come
and beg for their life if they want help.
And if I feel like it, maybe I'll
lend them the 20 empty services.
If they want to stay alive and healthy,
all they have to do is obey me, their king!
This way, no one will
dare challenge my rule.
And that is the perfect
way to govern a country.
This isn't real governing, Wapol,
and you aren't a real king!
Well, you certainly
speak your mind, Dalton.
Now kill him!
I want you to shoot your former captain!
As usual, you don't
understand a thing I'm saying.
I served your father before
you And he was always
a good man and a fair
ruler I hoped you might
come to resemble him one
day But I see now that
that was a lot of wishful
thinking Not good,
he's using the ox ox fruit
He's in his bison form
Don't back down, just fire him
We can't hit him He just dodges
No mercy, even to my ex-soldiers
Fiddle-Bam, attacking!
Amazing!
He's so powerful!
So this is the kind of power the
Zone-type Devil Fruit will give?
Enough!
I've had it with you
pathetic so-called rulers.
There can be no hope for a
country where the king and his men
are the first ones to abandon the
people during a time of crisis.
Let's see how well you do
fighting against the two of us.
Just give up.
Dalton!
Dalton, wait!
We've come to help you!
Please let us fight with you!
We're going to protect our country!
Remember, I've known you a long time.
And I know you well.
No, don't!
I know what your weaknesses are.
Oh no, why did you shield
us from that shot? Dalton!
Are you alright?
I told you I knew where
your weak spot was.
Nice guys always finish last.
Quite a fitting death, huh boys?
What's that?
Is that an earthquake?
This doesn't look good.
We won't be able to go any
further in this deep snow.
It seems like we've gone
partially up the mount.
What's this?
Why is the ground shaking?
Oh no, Usopp!
Is this what I think it is?
Inevolent!
It's 25,631, 32, 25,633.
What's going on?
What's all that rumbling?
25,633!
Damn, those stupid overgrown
buddies, I'm gonna kill them!
What are we supposed to do?
How do we get away from all this snow?
No clue.
All I know is that the
first priority is Nami,
the second priority is Nami,
and the third priority is Nami.
Got that, Luffy?
Protect her, even if it kills you!
I got it!
But how do I do that?
Over there!
Head for that cliff! Why?
Just run!
We need to get as high
up as we possibly can!
It's coming!
Good.
We made it up here just in time.
Oh no!
We aren't high up enough, Mubi!
This isn't good. Now
what? Oh, right. I know.
Sachi!
Grab a hole!
Thanks for that, Luffy.
Yeah, sure.
But what now?
Even if we don't sink in the snow, we're
just gonna keep flying down this mountain?
unless we do something about it.
No way.
I'm never gonna let that happen.
We've come all this way.
And we were almost to
the base of the mountain?
just feet away from the doctor.
Luffy, you need to come up with
a way to stop all this right now!
It's all because of those damn bunnies!
Next time I see them, I'm gonna
turn them into a big bowl of stew!
Ooh, rabbit stew?
That sounds good!
What do we do?
The only thing we can do at the moment!
Slide faster!
What is their problem?
Seriously!
Luffy, look out!
A rock!
We're gonna crash!
You can't crash into that thing!
You're the one in charge of
keeping Nami safe right now!
We're gonna crash!
Ladies get treated gently,
so you take care of her.
Sanji!
Soji!
That thing got me good.
What were you thinking?
Next time you do something
like that, warn me!
Soji!
It's coming!
It's not stopping!
The whole village will be swallowed up!
Get out of here!
We're going!
Koza, Kurimanimo, get on!
Robson, serious move!
Go!
Cape, sir, please!
You have to let us ride too!
Get away from there!
You can all find your own way out!
Robson, hurry!
It's closing in on us!
We'll be all right!
I promise, Phoebe!
Even if we get buried by this,
I'll be able to save you, I'm sure!
Luffy and the others headed
up in that direction, right?
Do you think the avalanche could
have already gotten to them?
We gotta go faster!
Thank you.
I don't know.
Nami, I'm sure you're cold.
Just hang in there a little longer.
Listen, hang on to this for me.
I'll be right back, okay?
Oh, it was you guys in there.
No wonder it had such a disgusting taste.
I won't let them get away with this.
Who are you talking about?
Them.
I'm talking about them, of course.
But who do you mean by them?
You told me earlier that some of the Straw
Hats headed up the
mountain toward my castle,
isn't that right?
Then this happened.
They have a grudge against us.
They're still mad about what happened.
So they climbed up there
and started an avalanche.
So, they were the ones who caused it?
Those sinister Straw Hat
pirates caused the avalanche.
That's right.
Well, boys, let's go.
We'll see if those
stupid sea-loving sailors
know anything about fighting in the snow.
Wow!
There we go!
I'll get you there, don't worry.
You just stay alive.
Both of you.
Up there!
I see the brats up ahead, Wapbles, sir.
Found you!
Now, I'll make you pay,
you damn Straw Hat!
Move it.
Heh, I don't think so.
Why would I want to do that?
I have no intention of
making it easy for you and
those half-dead friends of
yours to get away from here,
Straw Hat!
Hey!
Stop right there!
Ah, got it.
Hey, Chess, I've thought up a
new law to celebrate my return.
Write this down.
Right!
Anyone who ignores the
king will be executed.
Those three are guilty!
Chess, Korimai-mo, I want them
to be punished immediately!
Deal with the two unconscious ones first,
since they're ignoring me them all!
What did he say?
I've got the woman on his back.
I'll take the man.
Prepare for Marmo surprise.
Listen Luffy, I don't want you
fighting these guys, all right.
Nami will be able to
feel every move you make.
She's too sick to be able to
handle something like that.
It would be too much.
She could die.
Can't fight.
You're gonna regret this
later, don't follow me!
Huh, what a coward.
It's no use!
It's time he learned.
What a battle in the snow is like.
There's no one.
That's weird.
I wonder if they've already given up.
Here's what a snow battle's really like.
Snow powder makeup, the white disguise.
Those two are so incredibly weak
that just one shot should be enough.
Now it's checkmate. No!
Polar bears?
Loppins!
Did those things just protect him?
That's impossible.
Loppins never form bonds with humans.
They're nothing more than wild beasts.
Thanks a bunch!
You guys saved me!
Don't let him get away! Right!
What the hell are those stupid
bunnies doing standing there?
Doctor.
Doctor!
This is it.
It's tall and straight up.
But the doctor's up there,
so I gotta climb it.
All right, nami and sanji there's
just a little further to go?
What happened?
The avalanche it must have buried us.
There you are us up come on now
wake up you've got to wake up!
He's still alive, I'm going to get
you out of there who stop, okay?
Just hang on a bit longer
Come on us up, please just
wake up Snap out of it!
Just give me a few more
minutes here, Vivi.
I was in the middle of
such a lovely dream.
We were in a world far away from
here, sitting in a field of flowers?
with a beautiful river flowing next to it.
Oh!
You're crossing over into
the afterlife, Usopp!
You need to get out of that dream!
Now wake up!
Ah, look at the Usopp
pirates, all 74,000 of them.
They're such good, brave warriors.
Okay, get up now!
You have to wake up!
Do you hear me?
Usopp! Usopp!
Oh, wow.
You saved my life, Phoebe.
I was almost a goner there for a second.
I'm lucky to be alive.
That was a close one.
Really, so close.
Except that my face feels kind of swollen.
Why is that?
Oh, it's the cold.
That happens.
It's an unfortunate side
effect of a snowy area.
I don't know.
Maybe it's the cold or something.
What matters now is figuring out
where we are and what to do next.
Do you have any lip balm or anything?
Whoa, that was a close one.
Why do I feel like I dreamed
about a field of flowers?
Hit by an avalanche in the
middle of a training session.
Not exactly an ideal workout, but I guess
it is kind of like swimming in snow.
Zoro?
Oh, hey, VB. What's up?
Oh, it's you, Usopp.
What are you guys doing all
the way out here in the snow?
That's exactly what we
were going to ask you!
Take that, you stupid buddies!
You pathetic creatures got exactly what
you deserve for going up against the king!
Still,
it annoys me that I had
to expend so much of
my power against a pack
of overgrown rabbits!
There was no helping it, sir.
They are the fiercest
animals in Drum Kingdom.
And you're next!
STAWHAAAAAT!
Sachi!
That was...
That was warm.
Winter swimming?
Yeah, that was the idea anyway.
But after swimming in the river for a
while, I had no idea where I was anymore.
So I started walking around doing
some strength training workouts.
Dressed like that in cold weather?
You're real stupid, aren't you?
That isn't the point.
Now would you shut up and
give me your coat, Usopp?
Not a chance.
Maybe Nami's sick from the mental
exhaustion of dealing with these two.
And how about your shoes?
Nope.
Just one, then! I said no!
You did this to yourself!
Look at that, guys.
There's some people over there.
Huh?
Hey, look at those buildings.
They seem familiar, don't they? Huh?
You're right, Usopp.
This place is Bighorn.
We just came back.
It looks a lot different
buried in snow, though.
Stay back, all of you!
Dalton's already dead anyway.
It'd take more than a couple
flimsy arrows to kill hell.
You're his men, or used to be at least.
Don't you care at all about
what happens to Dalton?
Things have changed.
We're all Waple's soldiers now.
And any one of you who opposes
Wapol is as good as dead.
Hey, what's going on here?
What's going on here?
Wait what's going on with you
why are you dressed like that
Dalton is buried under the snow
that came down with the avalanche
what Dalton's under that that's
right and we can't get over
there to take him out because
those guys are blocking us for
the last time stay back but if
you really want to take your
friend up i guess you can go
ahead and try fighting us all hey
who's up i think i remember
their clothing those are the same
exact guys who attacked our ship
when we were out in the ocean
right oh yeah that's
right then they're the
enemy bad guys not our friends you follow
me yeah but wait a second i know that look
you aren't so brave without Dalton around?
No! Zoro! What are you doing?
Who's that guy?
You need to be careful.
Nothing good will come
from attacking them.
Oh, this is so warm.
I really like this thing.
That's why you wanted
to know who they were?
Watch out, Zoro!
They don't look very happy.
I know you.
You were on the ship with that guy
who beat up Womple, weren't you?
That's right.
You're a little slow, aren't you?
Oh, my God!
Hang on, you two.
We're almost there.
Don't you die on me.
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
Huh?
We're here.
Doctor...
EW!
Dr.
Young, the antibodies
seem to be responding.
Yes, as I guess they would.
The treatment worked, but what
was the cause of the illness?
Kestia.
Kestia, that's exactly correct.
Now you go and attend the girl, all right?
Yes.
Hello?
Thank you.